Lorenzo Arritola

Website: larritola.com

(770) 286 9445 lorenzoarritola@gmail.com

SUMMARY

6+ years of professional experience as a freelance videographer, working closely with clients to craft quality work that meets and exceeds expectations. Additionally, I am proficient in many skill sets through my educational background and am always eager to expand upon my accrued knowledge to become more well-rounded in my capabilities.

EXPERIENCE

Post Production Editor and Videographer Freelance

2018 - Present

- Edited 50+ professional-quality videos and promotional content for clients such as University of Arkansas, Oglethorpe University, etc.
- As the sole video editor of various projects, sorted and edited 10+ hours of raw footage into 10
 minutes of finished video per week, frequently to positive client response
- Interfaced routinely with clients throughout the creation process and utilized client feedback to produce compelling content that often exceeded client requests and expectations
- Frequently multitasked between several ongoing projects while adhering to tight deadlines
- On-site shoot experience producing and shooting commercial video content

Farm Hand, Aurora Dairies

2023 - 2024

Jay Buscaron, Manager

- Operated technical equipment for dairy production on daily schedule
- Routinely followed procedures in accordance with safety guidelines for proper dairy operation
- Drove cows to and from dairy shed utilizing UTVs
- Utilized heavy machinery such as tractor and combine for variety of farming needs
- Administered medication to livestock when sick

Instructor, Mathnasium - The Math Learning Center

2016 - 2019

- Todd Seibert, Business Owner
- Assisted students, ranging from elementary to high school, with understanding mathematical concepts and troubleshooting problems (both in one-on-one instruction and in groups)
- Helped to build student confidence in mathematics and improve mental structures for approaching mathematical concepts with an analytical mindset
- Assisted administration with routinely tidying up the facility, administered various tests to students, and continually updated records of student progress as milestones were achieved

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Possess excellent communication and interpersonal skills with others via dealing directly with clients on a consistent basis
- Continuously exploring and developing new skill sets with adventurous enthusiasm
- Quick to learn in fast-paced environments and tackle problems efficiently
- Knowledgable in programming languages such as Python, C, JavaScript, and Ruby (e.g., coded and designed my portfolio website, GitHub profile located at https://github.com/larritola1)

EDUCATION

Georgia State University, Atlanta, GA Bachelor of Arts, Film and Video GPA: 3.98, Graduated Summa Cum Laude 2018